{
    "id": "635c9c2f043b4becb0dc741e7a066a10",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns And Adverbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fb719c2c898549c2a0cca062a9eec215",
            "title": "Relative Pronouns And Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ".......................... she said made no sense to me.",
                    "description": "What means the thing that which.",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "That",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "All ............................ I want is something to eat.",
                    "description": "The relative pronoun that can refer to things. It is common after all, any etc.",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can give you ............................. you need.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She got married again after two months, ................................. made her parents angry.",
                    "description": "Which can modify an entire clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has acted in a movie ............................. name I don't remember.",
                    "description": "Whose replaces pronouns like his, her, its. He has acted in a movie. I don't remember its name. He has acted in a movie whose name I don't remember. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "whose",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has acted in a movie the name of ............................ I can't remember.",
                    "description": "The name of which means the same as whose name. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "whose",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He married a highly successful business woman ............................... you may have heard of.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whom",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He married a rich heiress of ............................... you may have heard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You know Mary ................................. mother is a writer?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "whose",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to see some old neighbors .............................. children I used to play with when I was small.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whose",
                        "that",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the girl ............................... sells books?",
                    "description": "In identifying relative clauses, that can refer to people in an informal style.",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is Janaki ................................. sells tickets?",
                    "description": "That cannot be used in non-identifying relative clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}